import { Question } from '../../model/question';

export const PAST_PERFECT_SIMPLE_CONTINUOUS: Question[] = [
  {question: 'I lived in Miami, Florida. I (lived) in New York City before.' , response: 'had lived'},
  {question: 'Remember that horrible day: You eventually arrived. I (wait) for you for two hours!', response: 'had been waiting'},
  {question: 'He (marry) her two years before we met.', response: 'had married'},
  {question: 'I (want / always) to travel. That\'s why I was delighted to go abroad with them.', response: 'had always wanted'},
  {question: 'We (stay) there since 1980, you know.', response: 'had been staying'},
  {question: 'I (stay / never) in London before. How expensive hotels are!.', response: 'had never stayed'},
  {question: 'Did I tell you that when I saw you, I realised that we (meet/already)?.', response: 'had already met'},
  {question: 'James told me you (buy) the old vicarage two years before your son\'s birth', response: 'had bought'},
  {question: 'I wish we (buy) it before.', response: 'had bought'},
  {question: 'She was no stranger to him. They (be introduce) to each other a few days before.', response: 'had been introduced'},
];
